Taxi Company: Good afternoon. Thank you for calling Express Taxis.
To book a taxi, press one. For customer service, press two.
Taxi Company: Hello. Express Taxis. How can I help?
Izzy: Hello. Can I book a taxi from one hundred and nine The Strand, please?
Taxi Company: Of course. Where to?
Izzy: Victoria Station.
Taxi Company: Train station or coach station?
Izzy: Train station.
Taxi Company: And when would you like it for?
Izzy: As soon as possible.
Taxi Company: OK. About ten minutes?
Izzy: Thanks. How much is it?
Taxi Company: That’s fourteen pounds.
Izzy: Can I pay by card?
Taxi Company: Yes, of course.
Izzy: Perfect. Thank you.
Ticket Clerk: Can I help?
Ben: Yes, can I have a ticket to Gatwick Airport, as soon as possible, please?
Ticket Clerk: No problem, the next train is at seventeen fifteen.
Ben: OK, that’s fine.
Ticket Clerk: Single or return?
Ben: Er…single.
Ticket Clerk: That’s eighteen pounds fifty. Cash or card?
Ben: Card, please.
Ticket Clerk: Do you need a receipt?
Ben: No, thank you. Which platform is it?
Ticket Clerk: Platform thirteen.
Ben: Thanks.